{
    "subject": "resource/Ivesia_pickeringii",
    "predicate": "ontology/genus",
    "object": "resource/Ivesia",
    "human_readable": "Ivesia pickeringii is a type of Ivesia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9394432306289673,
            "question": "Is Ivesia pickeringii a member of the Ivesia genus?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9227148294448853,
            "question": "What type of plant is Ivesia pickeringii?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8858625292778015,
            "question": "What is another name for Ivesia pickeringii?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8508315086364746,
            "question": "How is Ivesia pickeringii typically used or valued?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7907649874687195,
            "question": "To which genus does Ivesia pickeringii belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7697864770889282,
            "question": "What are some characteristics that distinguish Ivesia pickeringii from other Ivesia species?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6323409080505371,
            "question": "Are there any specific environmental conditions required for Ivesia pickeringii to thrive?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6267505288124084,
            "question": "What are the conservation status and threats facing Ivesia pickeringii?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6189215183258057,
            "question": "Where might Ivesia pickeringii be found growing naturally?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3347650468349457,
            "question": "Can you provide examples of other species within the Ivesia genus?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ivesia pickeringii is a type of Ivesia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_572_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where might Ivesia pickeringii be found growing naturally?",
            "html": "dbpedia_572_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the conservation status and threats facing Ivesia pickeringii?",
            "html": "dbpedia_572_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any specific environmental conditions required for Ivesia pickeringii to thrive?",
            "html": "dbpedia_572_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_572_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_572_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_572_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_572_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_572_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_572_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_572_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_572_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_572_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_572_5.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Ivesia pickeringii is a type of Ivesia.\" Both `10. Ivesia sericoleuca` and `23.txt` mention that Ivesia belongs to the genus of flowering plants, while `5.txt` lists \"Ivesia pickeringii\" as one of the species within this genus. Therefore, the triple is correct according to the provided documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}